Vladislav Karasev

vladislav0904@gmail.com +79220165900

Sankt-Petersburg, Russia

Codersrank: @Vladislav0904

GitHub: @Vladislav0904

Profile

With over years of experience in development, I am excited to apply my skills not only in building web applications but also in other areas. I am always willing to learn new technologies. In my spare time, I develop tools for games and do modding - it's my hobby that complements my professional path.

Experience

Reverse Engineering, Research, UX,: Mafia Hub 2022-Present

We are a team of passionate artists, designers, developers, and reverse engineers committed to delivering multiplayer modifications and tools to Mafia series games. We provide a modding framework dedicated to multiplayer experiences for Mafia The City of Lost Heaven, Mafia 3, and Mafia Definitive Edition.

JS/TS, Angular, HTML/CSS, Docker, Deployment, Figma

Backend, Data Architecture, UI/UX, Tools: NCRP 2018-2022

Role-Play server for the game Mafia II, based on M2O.

Electron, Squirel, SQLite, MySQL, Docker, Deployment, Apache, SVN, Git, GitHub, Figma

Research, Development, Testing: M20 2018-2022

Multiplayer modification of Mafia 2 Online for Mafia II.

C++, C, Git, GitHub, Figma

Projects

faqtly - Open-source | WIP

The project aims to automatically analyze the GitHub repository to find the most frequently asked questions and generate answers to them.

Python, Git, GitHub, REST, OpenAl, API, Data analysis

The Exchange Rate - Open-source

Desktop app that aims to show the exchange rates for currencies(some crypto included). Includes calculator for user and export to database and csv. Python, Git, GitHub, BS4, requests, Data analysis, pandas, csv, sqlite China Shop Town Bot - Closed-source

A small Telegram bot to order from Poizon.

Python, aiogram, Git, GitHub, API, Docker, Jenkins Deployment, PostgreSQL

The Estate Agent - Open-source

Graduation Project for Yandex.Lyceum - Web service that helps people to sign up for real estate tours and also provide estate agents an opportunity to modify estate objects

Python, Git, GitHub, REST API, Flask, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

Education

Peter the Great St. Petersburg Polytechnic University - Software Engineer, 2022 - Present

Yandex.Lyceum (Chelyabinsk, Russia) - Python Industrial Developer, 2019 - 2021

Skills

Languages: Main - Python, C++, Secondary - Lua, Squirrel, Java. Technologies: Web (HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Django, Flask), DB (SQL, SQLite, MySQL, PostreSQL), CI/CD (Docker, Jenkins), UI/UX (Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Abobe Illustrator), OS (Windows, Linux), VCS (Git, SVN, GitHub, GitLab), Desktop Development (Qt)